<resources>
    <string name="app_name">electricalCET</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="abtdept">About_department</string>
    <string name="ee">Vision \n
Be a centre of excellence and higher learning in Electrical Engineering and allied areas.\n
\n
Mission \n
Bring up professionally competent, ethically sound and service oriented Electrical Engineers having leadership qualities, aptitude for higher studies and research. \n


Program Educational Objectives \n
Graduates will \n

1. \n

excel as a technically competent Electrical Engineer \n

2. \n

excel in higher studies and build on fundamental knowledge to develop technical skills within and across disciplines. \n

3. \n

have the ability to function effectively as a member or leader in a
technical team. \n

4. \n

uphold social responsibilities and ethical values while solving
engineering problems. \n </string>
    <string name="about" > About Department \n
    The Department of Electrical Engineering is one of the founding departments of College of Engineering Trivandrum which started functioning in 1939.
    Right from its inception, the department has been rated very high in academic circles. provides quality technical education to young minds with a zeal to contribute to the advancement of human knowledge and progress. We, the students, staff and faculty at EE strive to take the global presence of CET to the next level. \n

      At present, the department runs undergraduate, graduate and doctoral programmes. All the programmes have been approved by All India Council for Technical Education (AICTE).
        The department is an approved QIP centre.Most students get placement in leading industries or organisations and get admission in reputed institutions in India and abroad for their higher studies. \n
        The deparment conducts a B.Tech programme, four M.Tech Programmes and PhD programme, all affiliated to APJ Abdul Kalam Technological University. \n
    </string>

</resources>
